(Sheldon:)Leonard, are you in the shower?
I can't hear you!
I'm in the shower!
(Sheldon:)I asked if you
were in the shower,
but that's moot now!
(Leonard:)What?
Moot! Rendered unimportant
by recent events!
I can't hear you!
I'm in the shower!
(Sheldon:)I have to skip
the chitchat.
(Sheldon:)Emergency.
(Leonard:)What kind of
emergency?
(Sheldon:)Mathematical--
32-ounce banana smoothie,
(Sheldon:)16-ounce bladder.
(Leonard:)You might not
want to do that.
(Sheldon:)I assure you I do.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I'm not alone in here.
What?!
(Priya:)Hello, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)What are you doing in there?
She can't be in here!
We were in here first;
you can't be in here.
(Sheldon:)According to
the roommate agreement,
(Sheldon:)paragraph nine, subsection B,
"The right
to bathroom privacy
(Sheldon:)is suspended in the event
of force majeure."
(Sheldon:)And believe me,
I am experiencing
a very majeure force.
(Sheldon:)Come on, you can't
wait two minutes?
(Priya:)Oh, Leonard,
let the man pee.
Penny? Penny?
(Sheldon:)Penny?
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)Move. Move. Move!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪